Guide to the United States Labor Education in the Americas Project (L.E.A.P) records, "1983-2013 LAC0016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Maquiladora/Sweatshop Campaigns, 1983-2008; Series 4
  - Phillips Van-Heusen Campaign, 1991-2001; Series 4 Subseries 1
    - Taking on Phillips-Van Heusen: Maquila Workers Fight for a Contract, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - PVH Campaign Supporter Kit, 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Canadian Labor Congress, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen closing [1/2], 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen closing [2/2], 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen communications, 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen conference call, 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Corporate DISTIMA, 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen form 10-K, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen pre-closing, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen worker statement, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Lessons from The Victor at Phillips Van Heusen by David Moburg, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Phillips Van Heusen, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/AIP NGO, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Bluca, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Bluref, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen board, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Camisas Milpas Altas, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Campaign for Labor Rights updates, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen campaign supporter kit, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen, Cardiz Study, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Carlos Arias, negotiations, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Clean Clothes Campaign/Gant, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen closing, rebuttal, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen, CEO Bruce Klatsky, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen contractors report, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Corporacin Mercantil del Caribe, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/CUSG, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen demonstrations, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen emails [1/2], 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen emails [2/2], 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen equipment removal, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen-Factory Closing coverage, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/GSP Petition, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Guatemala information and updates, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen, Honduras, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/ITGLWF, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen legal, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen, PIERS data [1/2], 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen shipping records [2/2], 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Human Rights Watch, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Interfaith Corporation for Corporate Responsibility, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen neutrality agreement, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Supreme International Corporation, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/United Students Against Sweatshops, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/UNITE, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/Yu-Yang campaign, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen Workers' Tour, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - VESTEX, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - SITRAIMASH/Phillips-Van Heusen, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen, Regis Philbin, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen/ USLEAP memoranda, 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen Annual Report, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Guatemala-Cardiz/Phillips-Van Heusen, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Affiliated Unions and Labor Publications, 1983-2011; Series 4 Subseries 2
    Materials in Boxes 126 to 129 are organized chronologically by year, ranging from 1983 to 2011. Materials from Boxes 130 to 134 are organized by alphabetically by title, with similiar titles marked by numbers in brackets to indicate their order. Dates reset across one title to another.
    - ILO Publication on Multinationals, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Human Rights-FENSUAGRO, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Labor Links Solidarity Committee, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Labor Party Advocates, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Labor Research Association, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Midwest Center for Labor Research, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - September 19th Union, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - SEIU Resolutions, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - United Farm Workers of America (UFW) pamphlet, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (U.E.) pamphlet, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Asia Workers Solidarity Links, 1983-1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Trade Union Rights-Surveys of Violations-International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1986-1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - International Trade Secretariats, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Fernand Braudel Center Review-Vol. XI, No.3-"The New Internationalism," by Peter Waterman, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - International Commission for the Coordination of Solidarity Among Sugar Workers (ICCSASW), 1988-1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Offprint: Socialism & Democracy-"The Labour Movement Library and Archive (ABA) in Copenhagen" by Gerd Callesen, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - CHDG International Bulletin-Labor Conflicts and Human Rights, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Center for the Progress of Peoples, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - Commitee for International Support of Trade Union Rights (CISTUR), 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - Commitee for Labor Access, 1989-1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - Farm Labor Organizing Committee, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - ICFTUA conference, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - International Conference on Strategies for Global Labor Solidarity, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - International Federation of Plantation, Agricultural, and Allied Workers (IFPAAW), 1989-1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - International Labor Rights (ILR) conference, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - Philippine Workers Support Committee, 1989-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - Southern Appalachian Labor School, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers (UAW), 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 26)
    - Association for Union Democracy, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 27)
    - Chicago Area Strike Solidarity Committee, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - National Postal Mailhandlers, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - Workers' Education Local 189, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 30)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 31)
    - International Federation of Commercial, Clerical, Professional and technical Employees (FIET), 1991; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 32)
    - International Federation ofJournalists, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 33)
    - International Groups, 1991-1995; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 34)
    - International Human Rights Law Institute-Doug Cassell, 1991-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 35)
    - ITGLWF, 1991-1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 126, Folder 36)
    - National Labor Committee-Charles Kernaghan and Barbara Briggs, 1991-1995; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Workers Education Local 189, 1991-1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - AFSCME, 1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Canadian Labor Congress, 1992-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - CWA, 1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - CRI-Child Labor, 1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers (IUE), 1992-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehouse Union (ILWU), 1992-1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Bakery, Confectionaery, and Tobacco Workers International Union (BCTWU), 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts Labor Commitee-Tess Ewing, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - The ILO-The Challenge for the 21st Century, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE), 1993-1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - United Food and Commercial Workers Union (UFCW), 1993-1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - United Public Employess Local 790-Margaret Shelleda, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - International Federation of Building and Wood Workerse (IFBWW) bulletins, 1994-1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - International Federation of Workers' Education Associations (IFWEA) bulletins, 1994-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - National Labor commitee-Haiti, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Trade Aid List, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - International Labor Office (ILO) complaint, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - ICTUR delegation, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - ITG affiliation application, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 21)
    - CLUW, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 22)
    - CLR Steering Committee, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 23)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 24)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 25)
    - International Transport Workers' Federation (ITF), 1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 26)
    - Korean Council of Economic Organizations, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 27)
    - Korean House for International Solidarity (KHIS), 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 28)
    - Maquila Solidarity Network, 2000-2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 29)
    - National Labor Committee, 2000-2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 127, Folder 30)
    - Taiwan contact information, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Union information, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - United for a Fair Economy (UFE), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Worker rights Consortium & Working Group, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - "A Declaration to Apparel Retailers"-UNITE Campaign Statement, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - ICFTU Surveys and reports, 2002-2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - International Worker Rights Caucus, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - ITGLWF Education Pack-Global Companies, Global Unions!, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - SIEU Local 1, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Hesperian Foundation-A Health Guide for Workers, 2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - International Handbook of Trade Unions, 2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, Comite Fronterizo de Obreras, 2004; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Escuela Nacional Sindical, 2004; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Rural Coalition brochure, 2004; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Globalization Run Amok-Investigative Report, 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Maquila Solidarity Network-Brand Campaigns and Worker Organizing, 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Maquila Solidarity Network conference, 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Reinventing Globalization Conference, 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Business for Social Responsibility Conference, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - International Globalization Conference, Puebla, Mexico, 2007; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Sustainable Anti-Sweatshop conference, 2007-2008; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - ILR and Globalization-Labor Studies Journal, 2007; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - New Labor Forum, 2007; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - UCLA Labor Center-Labor Education News, 2007; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 128, Folder 24)
    - Labor Studies Journal-Vol. 32 & 36, 2007-2011; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Imagining International Solidarity Conference, Dana Frank, 2008; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - International Labor Rights Forum-25 Years of Success, 2009; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - The American Prospect-Labor's New Globalization, 2010; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Centro de Apoyo al Trabajador (CAT), 2011; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Dominican Republic-Barrick Gold Corporation/USAS, 2011; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - American Center for International Labor Solidarity (ACILS), undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - ACTWU [1/2], 1993-1994; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - ACTWU and Clothing Manufacturers Association [2/2], 1993-1994; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - AFL-CIO-"Workers' Rights at the World Trade Organization and in US Trade Policy" (1), undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - THe AFL-CIO in Central America (2), 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - AFL-CIO Statement on Healthcare Reform (3), 1991; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - AFL-CIO American Institute for Free Labor Development (4), 1993-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - AFL-CIO Food and Allied Service Trade Department (5), 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - AFL-CIO Department of Field Mobilization (6), 1996-1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - AFL-CIO European Office (7), 1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - AFL-CIO Comments to FTAA (8), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - AFL-CIO and Globalization (9), 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - IUF news bulletins (1), 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - IUF/ITS conference (2), 1989; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - IUF International Labor Education Program: Participants' Syllabus (3), 1991; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - IUF International Labor Education Program: Facilitator's Syllabus (4), 1991; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - IUF International Labor Education Program: Background Material (5), 1991; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - IUF bulletins (6), 1994-1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - IUF Conference, Toronto (7), 1994; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - IUF North America Conference (9), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - IUF Education Manual -Getting to Grips with the Global Food Trade (9), 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - IUF/ Indonesia (10), 2005-2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - IUF Executive Committee, Geneva (11), 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Labor Coalition on Central America [1/2], 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Labor Coalition on Central America conference [2/2], 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Labor Notes (1), 1991-2004; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Labor Notes conference (2), 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Labor Notes-Cross Border Organizing (3), 1994; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Labor Notes-conference (4), 1995; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Labor Notes conference (5), 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Labor Notes conference (6), 2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - United Auto Workers (1), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - UAW Education Department: Taking Action in Global Economy (2), 2000-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - UAW-Taking Action in Global Economy (3), 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Unite Campaign Statement (1), 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - UNITE-Guatemala Research (2), 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - UNITE-invitation (3), 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Labor Mailings [1/2], 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Labor Mailings [2/2], 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Solidarity Center Maquila Meeting [1], 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Solidarity Center annual report [2], 2007; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Solidarity Center annual report [3], 2008; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - STITCH correspondence (1), 2000-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - STITCH planning (2), 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - STITCH Training, Nicaragua (3), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - United Students Against Sweatshops (USAS)-Alliance Building Committee (ABC), 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - USAS conference-Chicago, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - USAS conference packet, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - SUAS/USAS [1/3], 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - SUAS/USAS [2/3], 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - SUAS/USAS [3/3], 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - USAS/ Champion (1), 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - USAS committee (2), 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - USAS conference (3), 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - USAS Demographics (4), 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - USAS Student Labor Committee (5), 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - USAS Committee and conference call notes (6), 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - USAS conference leaflets (7), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - USAS conference materials and proposals (8), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - USAS conference report (9), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - USAS conference workshop (10), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - USAS International Committee (11), 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - USAS Listserv (12), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - USAS meeting (13), 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - USAS Conference Packet (14), 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - USAS disclosure emails (15), 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - USAS affiliates/International Solidarity Working Group (16), 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - USAS conference materials (17), 2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - USAS federated action (18), 2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - USAS campaign (19), 2005-2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - United Students Against Sweatshops International Intern Report (20), 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - United Students Against Sweatshops (USAS) conference materials (21), 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - USAS Union Factory List (22), 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - USAS Retreat (23), 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - United Students Against Sweatshops-Ten Years (24), 2008; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Labor Council for Latin America Advancement (LCLAA) report, 2011; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Affiliated Non-governmental Organizations, 1988-2010; Series 4 Subseries 3
    - Alliance for Community Media, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Bread for the World (German), undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Center of Concern, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Centre for Global Governance, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Lutheran Office for World Affairs, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Mozambique Support Network, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - New York Labor Religion Coalition, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Northern California Interfaith Council on Economic Justice and Work, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Trade Action Kit-WTO/GATT, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Woman of Hope, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Amnesty International USA, 1988-1992; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Center for Developing area Studies, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Food First Information and Action Netwrok (FIAN), 1988-1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Transafrica, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Transnationals Information Centre London, 1988-1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Asia Watch/ILR, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Blue Mountain Center, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Chicago Honduran Information Network, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 104, Folder 19)